Thomas O'Leary

Software Engineer

Full Stack developer with a passion for both client and server side programming. Recently deployed my first full stack web portfolio built with Django, React.js, Python, HTML & CSS. Proficient in Python with a background in market analytics, as well as multiple full stack projects. 4+ years experience creating business solutions as the only tech related employee for an automotive parts distributor. Currently looking for opportunities in web development with experience in JavaScript (Node, React), Python (API Development, Data Modeling, Flask, Django), Deployment (AWS, PythonAnywhere), HTML & CSS.



Contact

Address

Norton, MA, 02766

Phone

(774) 265-0484

E-mail

tom_oleary19@outlook.com

LinkedIn

https://www.linkedin.com/in/tom-oleary19/

GitHub

https://github.com/tom-oleary

Web Portfolio

www.troleary.com



Skills

Languages

Python | JavaScript | Java HTML | CSS | SQL | JSX

Libraries/Frameworks

React | Node | Django | Flask Bootstrap

Databases

PostgreSQL | SQLite | MySQL SQLAlchemy | Django ORM

Tools

Docker | Kubernetes | Git

General

CI/CD | Unit Testing



Work Experience

2016-05 -Current

Systems Analyst

Spring Rebuilders, Worcester, MA

- Deliver in-depth data analysis using SQL, Python and Pandas, increasing annual success rate on silent bidding contracts by 50%.
- Organize 2500 inventory items within relational databases used for comparison, calculations and market research.
- Improving company website by developing greater functionality through improved user interface design and convenient access to information.
- Develop reports to identify annual usages, OEM or aftermarket costs and freight policy, allowing for better allocation of resources to improve sales and profits.



2018-01 -

Education

2020-08	Buttered of Science. Computer Science
	Bridgewater State University - Bridgewater, MA
2016-01 - 2017-05	Computer Science
	Bristol Community College - Attleboro, MA
2011-09 - 2015-05	Physical Therapy
	University Of Tampa - Tampa, FL
2007-09 - 2011-05	High School Diploma
	Moses Brown School - Providence, RI

Bachelor of Science: Computer Science



Certifications

2021-01	Intermediate JavaScript, Udacity Nanodegree
	https://confirm.udacity.com/RR2AGQJK

2021-01 Full Stack Web Development, Udacity Nanodegree

February 2021 Expected Completion